(Sheldon:)Hello?
(Penny:)And that, girls, is how you make
a phony phone call.
(Amy:)I'm not sure I grasp
(Amy:)the full entertainment value,
but all right.
(Amy:)Next on Wikipedia's list
of slumber party activities:
"Truth or Dare."
(Penny:)Okay, it's your game.
You go first.
(Amy:)Hang on. I'm familiarizing
myself with the rules.
(Amy:)Seems fairly straightforward.
(Amy:)Bernadette, truth or dare?
(Amy:)Truth.
All right.
(Amy:)To what temperature
must you heat beef
(Amy:)in order to
kill the prion
(Amy:)that causes bovine
spongiform encephalopathy?
(Sheldon:)Um...
(Amy:)Remember, you have
to answer honestly.
(Penny:)Wait. No, Amy, you're
supposed to ask her
(Penny:)something personal
or embarrassing.
(Sheldon:)Oh.
(Amy:)All right.
(Amy:)What is the circumference
of your areolas?
"Munching on
complimentary popcorn.
Woot, woot."
(Sheldon:)Oh, the gall.
(Sheldon:)I hope his next tweet is
"Popcorn lodged in trachea.